var title = 'Numbers 10 to 19';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "10",
   answer: ["δέκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "11",
   answer: ["έντεκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "12",
   answer: ["δώδεκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "13",
   answer: ["δεκατρία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "14",
   answer: ["δεκατέσσερα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "15",
   answer: ["δεκαπέντε", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "16",
   answer: ["δεκαέξι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "17",
   answer: ["δεκαεπτά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "18",
   answer: ["δεκαοκτώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "19",
   answer: ["δεκαεννιά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];